<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="first_aid_title">Heart Attack First Aid</string>
    <string name="alone_title">Manage A Heart Attack When You Are Alone</string>
    <string name="quick_help">Quick Help</string>
    <string name="emergency_contact">Emergency Contact</string>
    <string name="nearby_health_facility">Nearby Health Facility</string>
    <string name="article">Article</string>
    <string name="edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="show_all">Show All</string>
    <string name="conscious_title_1">Don’t Panic</string>
    <string name="conscious_description_1">The main key to helping heart attack patients is not to panic. Immediately call an ambulance if you are unable to provide assistance.</string>
    <string name="conscious_title_2">Check The Patient\'s Consciousness</string>
    <string name="conscious_description_2">Call the patient\'s name several times while tapping on the shoulder. Patting the shoulder is done to ensure the patient\'s response. If the patient is conscious and responds immediately, place him in a sitting or lying position.</string>
    <string name="conscious_title_3">Give Medicine</string>
    <string name="conscious_description_3">Ask the patient whether he has routine medication or not. If there is immediately give the drug. Do not give other drugs because it will be very dangerous for his life.</string>
    <string name="conscious_title_4">Do Not Give Food Or Drink</string>
    <string name="conscious_description_4">Do not give food, drink, or massage to heart attack patients. you also should not wipe the patient\'s body with warm water, apply balm, or scrape the body of a patient with a heart attack. This action actually delays help or even worsens the patient\'s condition.</string>
    <string name="conscious_title_5">Take The Patient To The Doctor</string>
    <string name="conscious_description_5">Immediately take the patient to a hospital with access to a cardiologist so that he gets prompt and appropriate medical action</string>
    <string name="unconscious_title_1">Don’t Panic</string>
    <string name="unconscious_description_1">The main key to helping heart attack patients is not to panic. Immediately call an ambulance if you are unable to provide assistance.</string>
    <string name="unconscious_title_2">Check Pulse</string>
    <string name="unconscious_description_2">Check the carotid artery pulse which is located under the chin or the inside of the neck for 10 seconds. If it is not palpable or there is no pulse, it means cardiac arrest has occurred. Immediately call for help by calling an ambulance or asking the closest person to prepare a car to take him to the hospital.</string>
    <string name="unconscious_title_3">Heart Massage</string>
    <string name="unconscious_description_3">While waiting for an ambulance or vehicle to transport you to the hospital, you can provide assistance in the form of cardiac resuscitation or cardiac massage. Cardiac resuscitation is a medical aid step to restore the function of breathing or blood circulation in the body which has stopped. Cardiac resuscitation (CPR) aims to keep blood and oxygen circulating throughout the body.</string>
    <string name="independent_handling_title_1">Don’t Panic, Keep Calm</string>
    <string name="independent_handling_description_1">Stop all kinds of activities that are being done, then find a safe place to rest. If possible, choose one near the door or within easy reach of the emergency medical team. For example, while driving, pull over to the side of the road and ask passers-by for help</string>
    <string name="independent_handling_title_2">Call Medical Help</string>
    <string name="independent_handling_description_2">After resting, as much as possible contact emergency services or people as soon as possible so that medical help can be given immediately. With prompt medical treatment, damage to the heart muscle can be minimized</string>
    <string name="independent_handling_title_3">Take Aspirin</string>
    <string name="independent_handling_description_3">While waiting for medical help to arrive, take aspirin or blood thinners prescribed by a doctor. This drug can increase the chance of survival when faced with a sudden heart attack</string>
    <string name="independent_handling_title_4">Lie Down And Rest</string>
    <string name="independent_handling_description_4">After taking blood thinners or heart medications that are usually provided by doctors for emergency heart attack situations, lie down and rest while waiting for help to arrive.</string>
    <string name="first_aid">First Aid</string>
    <string name="independent_handling">Independent Handling</string>
    <string name="notification">Notification</string>
</resources>